Guide to the Silliman College, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Silliman College, Yale University, photographs
1939-1940
RU 601
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
6
The materials consist of photographs and slides documenting the construction of Silliman College at Yale. Included are interior and exterior views and photographs of the master's house.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 46-B (YRG 46-B), Records and materials documenting individual Yale buildings, facilities, and grounds.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged in four series: I. Construction Progress Photographs, 1939-1940. II. General Views, 1939-1940. III. Oversize. IV. Slides and transparencies; folio.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of photographs and slides documenting the construction of Silliman College at Yale. Included are interior and exterior views and photographs of the master's house.
College buildings -- Design and construction; Photographs; Slides (photographs); Silliman College (Yale University); Yale University -- Pictorial works; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University -- Student housing
- Construction progress photographs, 1939 - 1940; Series I
  - 1939 June: excavation (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1939 July-August (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1939 September-October (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1939 November-December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1940 January-February (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1940 March-April (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1940 May-June (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1940 July: exterior and courtyard views (Box 1, Folder 8)
- General views, 1939 - 1940; Series II
  - Construction views (general), 1940 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Exterior, from street, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Courtyard, 1940, n.d (Box 2, Folder 3 - 4)
  - Master's House, 1940, n.d (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Master's House, interior, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Interior, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Architects' drawing (from Alumni Magazine ), 1939 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Oversize, Series III
  - Bryers Hall (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Vanderbilt Hall (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Silliman College (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Slides and transparencies, Series IV
  - Slides (Box 4)
- Folio, Series IV
  - Signed etching by Louis Orr (Box DR25F82)